# **QUEEN OKORONKWO**

okoronkwonmesoma@gmail.com | +234 (0) 813 890 8884 | Ajoku Street, Owerri, Imo State LINKEDIN: https://tinyurl.com/linkedin-ok-queen

## **PERSONAL SUMMARY**

Digital Marketing Specialist with 4+ years' experience in SEO, content marketing, and social media management. Track record of driving business growth through data-led marketing campaigns. Led a campaign that increased visibility for Nigeria's largest wellness brand, Damos Wellness, through engaging video ads. Trained over 2,000 marketers in the past 4 years, shaping the next generation of digital marketing talent.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Graphic design/Video Editing: Canva, Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator)
- Analytical tools: MS Excel, Power Bl.

#### **EDUCATION**

2020 - present - **B.Sc., Medical Radiography**, Federal University Owerri, Nigeria (Expected 2024) 2014 - 2020 - **SSCE WAEC**., Federal Government Girls College Owerri, Nigeria

# **RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE**

Charioth Express Limited March 2024 - Sept 2024
Chief Marketing Officer Remote

- Designed a comprehensive marketing structure to optimise resource allocation and operations.
- Managed content calendars and oversaw Instagram marketing efforts.
- Achievement: Developed a strategic 6-month roadmap outlining content goals and objectives.

Damos Wellness 2021 - present

Role: Content Lead Remote

- Contributed innovative ideas in brainstorming sessions, resulting in the successful launch of three marketing campaigns and improved brand positioning.
- Collaborated with influencers, expanding social media post reach and increasing follower engagement significantly.
- Achievement: Improved brand awareness by 25% through successful video marketing campaigns.

Becomm Group 2022 - 2024

# **Role: Digital Marketing Specialist**

Remote

- Expanded brand reach and engagement by strategically partnering with influential figures in the industry.
- **Achievement**: Executed highly effective organic and paid social media campaigns that resulted in over 200 leads converted to sales within two months.

## **REFERENCES**

Available on request.